[
  {
    "question": "How does it feel to be a woman in STEM?",
    "answer": "It feels awesome! I hope I am motivating some of you to become interested in these fields.",
    "links": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Have you made any games?",
    "answer": "Yes I have made a few simple games!",
    "links": [
      "https://maribelduran.github.io/simon-game",
      "https://maribelduran.github.io/tic-tac-toe"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which University do you recommend?",
    "answer": "A university that gives you the opportunity to work on real world projects. I love all of the UC schools. However, the most important thing here is to attend a university :) ",
    "links": []
  },
  {
    "question": "How many languages do you know?",
    "answer": "Two languages: English and Spanish.",
    "links": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Have you ever been to Egypt?",
    "answer": "Not yet, but hoping to visit within the next 5 years!",
    "links": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you hack games?",
    "answer": "I cannot hack games.",
    "links": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you give me any tips on coding because I am interested and in a coding class now?",
    "answer": "That's exciting! A few tips: 1) Ask for help when you get stuck 2) Be patient. It can be hard in the beginning 3) Don't give up 4) Have fun!",
    "links": []
  },
  {
    "question": "How many countries have you been to?",
    "answer": "I have been to 11 countries so far!",
    "links": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Which college did you go to?",
    "answer": "University of California, Merced. Go Bobcats!",
    "links": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is your favorite place to travel so far?",
    "answer": "That is a tought question! I will have to choose London because there is always so much to do there and I used to visit there alot when I lived in Europe.",
    "links": []
  },
  {
    "question": "How long have you been in your career field?",
    "answer": "A little over 4 years now!",
    "links": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Tips for coding?",
    "answer": "A few tips: 1) Ask for help when you get stuck 2) Be patient. It can be hard in the beginning 3) Don't give up 4) Have fun!",
    "links": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you know of any coding challenges for me to do?",
    "answer": "Yes below are a few good places to code!",
    "links": [
      "https://code.org/learn",
      "https://www.brainpop.com/games/blocklymaze/",
      "https://www.madewithcode.com/projects/"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you work with a lot of other women in the STEM field?",
    "answer": "I work with very few women in this field. I encourage women to give this field a chance. It is a very exciting place to be in my opinion!",
    "links": []
  },
  {
    "question": "What are your favorite animals?",
    "answer": "DOGS! WOOF WOOF!",
    "links": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Is coding hard to learn?",
    "answer": "In my opinion, coding can be hard. It takes alot of effort and practice, but it is also very fun an provides many job opportunities.",
    "links": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you know chemistry and physics?",
    "answer": "Yes I do!",
    "links": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Out of all the places you’ve been, what’s your favorite?",
    "answer": "It is too hard for me to choose one! So I'll choose two. 1) Barcelona: beautiful city, amazing food, and wonderful people. 2) London: So much to see and do!",
    "links": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is your favorite basketball player? Team?",
    "answer": "Stephen Curry and the Golden State Warrios. GO WARRIORS! ",
    "links": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you like your job? PS I know Mr. Goolsby (LOL)?",
    "answer": "I am enjoying my current job. Mr. Goolsby is the best!",
    "links": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you like to run?",
    "answer": "Love to run!",
    "links": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you like to have fun? (LOL)",
    "answer": "I love to have fun!",
    "links": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Any tips for being successful in college?",
    "answer": "The number one tip is to not be afraid to fail. Even if a project is hard, you should still give it your best to finish a project. The most important thing you can do is try.",
    "links": []
  },
  {
    "question": "Where do you like to hike?",
    "answer": "I like to hike where there are waterfalls or hikes near the ocean!",
    "links": []
  },
  {
    "question": "What is your greatest record in running?",
    "answer": "My fastest half marathon (13.1 miles) time was 1 hour and 56 minutes.",
    "links": []
  },
  {
    "question": "How did you get into computer programming and why do you like it?",
    "answer": "I had my first computer programming class in college because it was part of the engineering course and I fell in love. I always loved technology so it is so much fun being able to combine science and technology.",
    "links": []
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the key to getting to where you are now?",
    "answer": "I think being kind, helping others, and working hard has helped me to getting where I am now.",
    "links": []
  }
]
